

ABOUT ME

I am a Full Stack Developer from Peru living in Spain. My interest in technology and involvement with it go back as far as I can remember. After years experience in Marketing and Sales, I made the best decision to turn my hobby into my profession.

SKILLS

HTML5 Docker CSS3 MySQL SASS Gulp Javascript Git React Js Agile Express Js Scrum Slack Ejs MongoDB Canva

SOFTSKILLS

TeamWork Client Focus Empathy Attention to detail Problem Solving Adaptability Quick

Positive learner attitude

LANGUAGES

Spanish **English** Native Professional

Francesca Bentin

Full Stack Developer

+34 635475139

francescabentin@gmail.com

 \oplus francescabentin.github.io/portfolio/ in Ω





EXPERIENCE

Adalab | Remote | January. 2023 - April 2023

Full-Stack Developer

- Layout: HTML5, CSS3, Sass, Responsive Design, Flexbox, CSS Grid.
- Javascript (ES6) and creation of a SPA with React.
- Developing a basic API with Node JS and Express JS.
- Version control with Git.
- Project development under SCRUM; framework and Agile philosophy.
- Development tools: Gulp, Visual Studio Code. Terminal, Zeplin, Render
- Communication skills and team work: Slack. Github.

Booksy Spain | 2022

Sales Consultant

Travelling | 2019 Personal experience

British American Tobacco Lima | 2016 - 2018 Trade Marketing rep

Mondelez Spain. | 2020 - 2021 Trade marketing rep

Enterprise Rent a car Mallorca

Customer and sales agent

Cool Trends | 2014 - 2016 Account manager

Kimbery Clark | 2011 - 2013 Trade marketing rep

EDUCATION

Web Development Bootcamp Adalab | 2023

Business Administration University of lima | 2009 - 2014

LATESTS PROJECTS



Website for a Brand, Personal project HTML, CSS, SASS



Presentation cards Apil HTML, CSS, SASS, Javascript, gulp



Harry Potter fan search Apil HTML, CSS, SASS,REACT



Proyects data manager Apil HTML, CSS, REACT, Node Js, Express, SQL, render por deployment





Hangman Game Api | HTML, CSS, SASS, REACT, NPM